[INTRO] About 70-80% of beginners. Those who loosen tail edge grip at the beginning of the turn.
[INTRO] Ah .. This is because I can't see the pelvis well.
[INTRO] The legs are brought close and the pelvis seems to rotate,
[INTRO] The pelvis doesn't actually rotate at all
[INTRO] Because it's an unusual method....
[INTRO] I'm careful to tell you
[INTRO] I'm using this method....
Hello. I'm Kim Seung-won
Last time we learned about equipment settings.
Now let's talk about BBP
Before we get to know BBP
Usually beginners ... so ...
Just those who are self-taught
Let's see why heel side turn is chattering.
Most beginners who start Forward-Carving
They know one needs the pelvic rotation, but...
they don't know how to properly rotate the pelvis
They have to enter heel side turn with pelvis already rotated,
but they fail to do it properly, so heel side edge is lost
Through this front leg stretch
They have to prevent them weight from leaning forward, but They couldn't.
If a resistance occurs to the nose without the pelvis rotation,
the pelvis will lean forward like this.
Then the tail doesn't get enough pressure,
the result being the edge in tail section will wash out.
70-80% of beginner's who loosen the tail edge has forward shifted weight in the beginning of the turn.
The main reason why that happens
is they can't do this pelvic rotation properly,
so they can't stretch their front leg.
Then, the tail is made edge grip properly.
So the tail loosens the edge.
Usually, people say in Forward-Carving,
"If you're good at basic carving, you're half way there."
Many people think
"Why can't I ride even though I'm good at basic carving?"
Most common cause is the pelvic rotation I mentioned.
I think you will definitely get better
if you take care of the pelvic rotation from the BBP stage.
Ok, then..
BBP, also called neutral position
About Balanced Body Position
Let me explain
Balanced Body Position is balanced,
It means a balanced basic posture.
If I take the BBP,
Spread as much as my stance,
assuming that the binding angle is set like this,
Open the upper body lightly by the angle of the forelegs,
The rear leg leans slightly on the boot
Lightly lean on the boot.
You don't have to lean too hard. Just lean a little bit
When you lean, your pelvis is ...
Don't just lean
Make sure your pelvis is over the rear boot.
Basically, lean like this with the thought
that your pelvis should be over the rear boot.
The front leg stretchs to fit the position.
The basics are like this.
And open the upper body
head directly over the front boot?
If you take this pose
This is a normal BBP posture. And..
This BBP posture also depends on this riding style and riding situation,
You can have a low BBP posture,
There also is a high BBP posture
Even though the height is different
All of these are BBP, that is neutral position
But as I mentioned before,
I tend to pay attention to pelvic rotation from the BBP training stage.
In general widely-accepted theory,
open the upper body only as much as the front binding angle dictates.
But, beginners are not used to the pelvic rotation
So, most of the time no matter how you practice your BBP posture,
If you ride it, just basic carving will loosen the pelvis like this.
If you ride heel side turn improperly, your upper body won't open.
This is because the pelvic rotation is not used at all.
So in my case, even if you practice BBP at home,
try your best to do the pelvic rotation.
A little too much
Try to open the pelvis more than the front binding angle
If you practice while try to open the upper body
as close to the vertical on the board as possible.
When you ride it, the pelvis won't loosen naturally
With the pelvis open like this,
you can do basic carving or riding.
Now ...
I want to tell you how to do pelvic rotation.
I'll shoot the camera in first person view
I can't see the pelvis, so I take off the top.
When most beginners rotate the pelvis
Misunderstanding is
when doing pelvic rotation,
Many people assume that they should "fold rear knee".
Folding it like this
The legs are brought close, the pelvis seems to rotate,
Actually the pelvis doesn't rotate at all
Just folding (pushing in) the rear knee
never get a pelvic rotation.
What you need to care about is not getting your knees close
To rotate the pelvis like this.
Don't gather knees.
Even when you're stretching your legs,
you just rotate the pelvis like this.
Doing basic carving you have to keep riding in this position
Rotate the pelvis, and the BBP posture leans the rear boot slightly.
Put the pelvis over the rear of the boot
Now this posture is very very important
When you first practice the BBP posture, do not sit comfortably like this.
Sit rear with the pelvis as far as possible,
Remember this sensation, the tension in muscles
you must be applied when riding
Lastly, I want you to practice your BBP posture a lot at home.
You can practice by looking in the mirror
I told you to put the pelvis up in the rear over the boot
And, you thought you put your pelvis over the rear boot
But, you're more likely not to be over the rear boot in fact.
Too far back
Too far forward
In actually, it's quite common to not be able to stay over the boot.
So take a look at a big mirror in your house and stand sideway.
Whether you have a pelvis over my rear boot or not
And whether your head is over front boot or not
You do a lot of up and down exercises like this,
BBP posture. Practice a lot of BBP posture depending on the height
(Camera team saying) Just do the posture one more time
Standing in front of a big mirror,
Rotate the pelvis
Leaning slightly rear boot, the pelvis put over that boot
Because it is harder to put the pelvis over the boot than you thought
You may have to think that the pelvis should be over the tail side more than the boot.
LG: no idea what you mean
First look at the mirror
Put the pelvis over the rear boot, head to the front
This posture is the basic posture
If the posture goes up, the pelvis will come a little bit forward.
That much, Get your head closer to the center from the front boot
up
down
You do this practice in the mirror
BBP Posture. Familiarize yourself with the position of the pelvis rotated.
I'm careful to say you because the method I told you is not general.
Trust me because I've been teaching heel side turn to ride stably through this method.
With this pelvic rotation
overdo it from the BBP stage
Do the pelvic rotation as much as you can
I will tell you about basic carving later
Even in the basic carving stage,
I will tell you to overdo much pelvic rotation a little.